(Amy:)Sheldon, what are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)You didn't respond
to any of my electronic communications.
(Amy:)I wanted to be alone.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to talk about it?
And keep in mind that "no"
is a perfectly viable answer.
(Leonard:)Sheldon,
my world is crumbling around me.
(Sheldon:)Point of order.
(Sheldon:)As you're in distress...
(Sheldon:)...it would be customary
for me to offer you a hot beverage.
(Sheldon:)But I'm a guest in your home...
(Sheldon:)...so it would be customary
for you to offer me a beverage.
How do you wanna proceed
vis-á- vis beverages?
(Amy:)It doesn't matter. Nothing matters.
(Sheldon:)If you'd like to take your mind off
what's troubling you...
(Sheldon:)...uh, word on the street is
a bobcat has been spotted.
(Amy:)Penny and Bernadette went shopping
for bridesmaids dresses without me.